# GÜRKAN HÜRAY

SECURITY & RISK PROFESSIONAL



# CONTACT

+420 605 955 141

gurkanhuray@gmail.com



# SOCIAL



linkedin.com/in/gurkanhuray

# **PRO SKILLS**

**IRAM** SGOP COBIT **ISO 27X** PCI-DSS Information Security Cyber Security Risk Management IT Strategy Compliance Internal Audit **Business Continuity** 

A list of complete skill set can be found in the LinkedIn profile for my proficiency.

Disaster Recovery

**GDPR** 

### **PROFILE**

Experienced Security and Risk Professional who worked in multi-national companies with a demonstrated history of working in the technology, finance, paper-and-forest products sectors. Skilled in many invaluable areas as described in the 'Pro Skills' section. Participated in many different initiatives, including for auditing purposes in Japan, Romania and Ukraine. Has a solid working background in internationally recognised standards and frameworks, including ISF's IRAM, SGOP - NIST's CSF. A solid contributor to the implementation of risk and control frameworks. Leading the ISMS program, designing and developing risk practices from scratch in the current position. Turkish and English speaker.

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# Stora Enso Czechia

Nov 2019 - Present

Senior Manager, Information and Cyber Security - Risk Jan 2019 - Nov 2019 Information Security and Risk Manager

- · Leading development work to improve the quality of Information Security and Cyber Security in the organisation.
- · Supporting the CISO in designing, implementing and maintaining an ISMS and enhancing the effectiveness of risk management and related IS governance processes.
- Supporting business process owners and service managers in the execution of the Information Risk Management process.

#### 2015 - 2018

# Nationale-Nederlanden Turkey

Senior Information Risk Management Specialist

- · Being responsible for maintaining the IT Risk Framework and its associated controls and reporting. That includes Risk Identification, Assessment and Evaluation, Risk Response, Risk Monitoring, IS Control Design and Implementation, IS Control Monitoring and Maintenance, IS Policies/Governance and Compliance, BCM and DRP coordination.
- · Being accountable to evaluate overall information technology risk, keep an active view, and report on the actual, mitigated and residual risk in the technology organisation.

#### 2010 - 2015

#### **IBM Turkey**

IT Security Specialist

- · Directly involved in internal/corporate audits against auditors as process owner of various security domains (based on internationally recognised frameworks/standards).
- · Leading implementation of third-party tools such as CyberArk to address specific security-related concerns.
- · Acting as an SME for the EMEA region to provide best practices.

# 2009 - 2010

# **IBM Turkey**

Technical & Customer Services Representative

· Supporting clients & employees in all technical delivery services. Additionally, acting as a focal for IT requirements

#### **EDUCATION**

2021 - 2023

University of Essex Online, UK

Cybersecurity, MSc

2004 - 2007

Afyon Kocatepe University, Turkey Industrial Electronics, Associate Degree